<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidDevPractice</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="wrong_password">Wrong Password</string>
    <string name="place_holder_instructions">Click on an icon to move it to the center and in large it.</string>
    <string name="WhatIsMotionLayout">Motion Layout is a subclass of Constraint Layout, bridging he gap between layout transitions and complex motion handing, offering a mix of features between the property, animation framework, TransitionManager and Coordinator layout.</string>
    <string name="what_is_a_radio_button">RadioButton: is a two state button that can be checked or unchecked. Once check the user can\'t uncheck it.</string>
    <string name="what_is_a_radio_group">RadioGroup: is a multiple-exlusion scope for a set of radio buttons. Checking one RadioButton in the group will uncheck an previously checked button in the same group.</string>
    <string name="preference_file_key">AndroidDevPracticeFile</string>
    <string name="what_is_a_toggle_button">Toggle Button: Allows the user to change a setting between two states.</string>
    <string name="off">OFF</string>
    <string name="on">ON</string>
    <string name="what_is_a_switch">Switch: Is a two-state toggle switch that can select between two options. The user may drag a thumb back and forth of tap to toggle. Switch compat is backwards compatible to API 7.</string>
    <string name="what_is_a_tool_tip">ToolTip: A Tool tip is a small is a small descriptive message that appears near a view when users long press the view or hover their mouse over it.</string>
    <string name="what_is_a_notifiation">Notification: provides short, timely information about events in your app while it\'s not in use.</string>
    <string name="what_is_a_category_call">CATEGORY_CALL: incoming call or similar synchronous communication request</string>
    <string name="what_is_a_cateogory_alarm">CATEGORY_ALARM: Alarm or timer</string>
    <string name="what_is_a_category_event">CATEGORY_EVENT: Notification category calendar event</string>
    <string name="what_is_Notification_priority">Notification Priority: Is an indication of how much of the user\'s valuable attention should be consumed by this notification.</string>


    <string-array name="notification_priority">
        <item>DEFAULT</item>
        <item>HIGH</item>
        <item>LOW</item>
        <item>MAX</item>
        <item>MIN</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>