<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidDevPractice</string>

    <string name="wrong_password">Wrong Password</string>

    <string name="preference_file_key">AndroidDevPracticeFile</string>

    <string name="off">OFF</string>
    <string name="on">ON</string>


    <!--Activity-->
    <string name="activity_summary">An activity is a single focused thing that the user can do. Activities interact with the user, so the Activity class takes care of creating a window fro you in which you can place your UI with setContentView. Activities are oftten presented to the user as full screen windows they can also be used in other ways as floating windows</string>
    <string name="activity_configuration_change_summary">Configuration change occurs when the orientation of the device changes, a configuration change results in reloading of the activity and a new layout depending on orientation. You can create you unique layouts for portrait or lands scape mode.</string>









    <!--User Interface  layout resources-->
    <string name="ui_switch_summary">Switch: Is a two-state toggle switch that can select between two options. The user may drag a thumb back and forth of tap to toggle. Switch compat is backwards compatible to API 7.</string>
    <string name="ui_tool_tip_summary">ToolTip: A Tool tip is a small is a small descriptive message that appears near a view when users long press the view or hover their mouse over it.</string>
    <string name="ui_notification_summary">Notification: provides short, timely information about events in your app while it\'s not in use.</string>
    <string name="ui_category_call_summary">CATEGORY_CALL: incoming call or similar synchronous communication request</string>
    <string name="ui_category_alarm_summary">CATEGORY_ALARM: Alarm or timer</string>
    <string name="ui_category_event">CATEGORY_EVENT: Notification category calendar event</string>
    <string name="ui_system_ui_summary">The System UI is screen bars dedicated to the display of notification, communication of device status, and device navigation. Typically the system bar displayed concurrently with the app.</string>
    <string name="ui_toast_summary">Toast: is a view containing a quick little message for the user, the view appears as a floating view over the application.</string>
    <string name="ui_snackbar_summary">Snackbar: Is attached to a view. The snackbar provides basic functionality if it is attached to any object derived from the view class. *** Snackbar</string>

    <string name="ui_motion_layout_summary">Motion Layout is a subclass of Constraint Layout, bridging he gap between layout transitions and complex motion handing, offering a mix of features between the property, animation framework, TransitionManager and Coordinator layout.</string>
    <string name="ui_radio_button_summary">RadioButton: is a two state button that can be checked or unchecked. Once check the user can\'t uncheck it.</string>
    <string name="ui_radio_group_summary">RadioGroup: is a multiple-exclusion scope for a set of radio buttons. Checking one RadioButton in the group will uncheck an previously checked button in the same group.</string>
    <string name="ui_toggle_button_summary">Toggle Button: Allows the user to change a setting between two states.</string>


</resources>